const questions = {
    "FOOD AND CUISINES": [
    {
        question: "1.	Which fruit has the highest protein content?",
        answer: "GUAVA"
    },
    {
        question: "2.	What is the main ingredient in “rajma curry”??",
        answer: "KIDNEY BEANS"
    },
    {
        question: "3.	What type of pasta has a name that means 'little worms'?",
        answer: "VERMICILLI"
    },
    {
        question: "4.	Which food is traditionally used as the main protein in a Vietnamese 'pho' soup?",
        answer: "BEAF OR CHICKEN"
    },
    {
        question: "5.	What is the main ingredient in the Spanish dish 'gazpacho'?",
        answer: "TOMATOES"
    },
    {
        question: "6.	What is the traditional French pastry made from croissant dough and filled with almond paste called?",
        answer: "ALMOND CROISSANT"
    },
    {
        question: "7.	What fruit is known as the ‘King of Fruits’ in Southeast Asia?",
        answer: "DURAIN"
    },
    {
        question: "8.	Which spice gives \"dal tadka\" its bright yellow color?",
        answer: "TURMERIC"
    },
    {
        question: "9.	Which Indian dessert is made from condensed milk and is shaped into round balls?",
        answer: "GULAB JAMUN"
    },
    {
        question: "10.	Which Indian dish is often referred to as butter chicken in the West?",
        answer: "MURGH MAKHANI"
    },
    {
        question: "11.	Which Indian flatbread is made using a mixture of wheat flour and mashed potatoes?",
        answer: "ALOO PARATHA"
    },
    {
        question: "12.	Which popular Indian dessert is made by deep-frying dough and soaking it in sugar syrup?",
        answer: "JALEBI"
    },
    {
        question: "13.	Which street food dish from Mumbai combines puffed rice, sev, and tamarind chutney",
        answer: "BHELPURI"
    },
    {
        question: "14.	What is the base ingredient in the popular South Indian dish Idli?",
        answer: "FERMENTED RICE AND URAD DAL"
    },
    {
        question: "15.	Which Indian spice blend is named after a city in Maharashtra and is used to flavor \"Misal Pav\"?",
        answer: "KOLHAPURI MASALA"
    },
    {
        question: "16.	Which leafy vegetable is used as the main ingredient in the Punjabi dish \"Sarson ka Saag\"?",
        answer: "MUSTARD GRAMS "
    },
    {
        question: "17.	What is the primary spice used in making \"Chai Masala\"?",
        answer: "CARDOMMOM"
    },
    {
        question: '18.	What is "Rasam," and in which part of India is it commonly consumed?',
        answer: "SOUTH"
    },
    {
        question: "19.	Which type of rice is most commonly used in making \"Biryani\"?",
        answer: "BASMATHI RICE"
    },
    {
        question: "20.	Which Indian street food is often referred to as \"water balls\"?",
        answer: "PANIPURI"
    }

    // Add more general knowledge questions...
],
"SPORTS": [
    {
        question: "1. Who is known as the \"Fastest Man inn the World\"?",
        answer: "USAIN BOLT"
    },
    {
        question: "2. Which country is known for the traditional sport of \"Sumo\"?",
        answer: "JAPAN"
    },
    {
        question: "3. In which sport do teams compete for the Stanley Cup?",
        answer: "ICE HOCKEY"
    },
    {
        question: "4. In which city were the 2024 Summer Olympics held",
        answer: "PARIS"
    },
    {
        question: '5. Which sport uses the terms "birdie," "eagle," and "bogey"?',
        answer: "GOLF"
    },
    {
        question: "6. Who is the only Indian to have won a medal in javelin throw at the Olympics?",
        answer: "NEERAJ CHOPRA"
    },
    {
        question: "7. Who is the first Indian woman to win a medal in the Olympics?",
        answer: "KARNAM MALLESHW"
    },
    {
        question: "8. Which Indian cricketer is known for his famous \"scoop shot\"?",
        answer: "MS DHONI"
    },
    {
        question: "9. Which Indian footballer is the captain of the national team and plays for Bengaluru FC?",
        answer: "SUNIL CHHETRI"
    },
    {
        question: "10. Which Indian cricketer is known as the \"Little Master\"?",
        answer: "SUNIL GAVASKAR"
    },
    {
        question: "11. Who is known as the \"Flying Sikh\" of India?",
        answer: "MIKHA SINGH"
    },
    {
        question: "12. In which year did the Indian cricket team win the T20 World Cup?",
        answer: "2007"
    },
    {
        question: "13. Which country has won the most Olympic medals in history?",
        answer: "US"
    },
    {
        question: "14. Who is the first woman to win an Olympic medal in boxing?",
        answer: "MARY KOM"
    },
    {
        question: "15. What is the national sport of Canada?",
        answer: "LACROSSE"
    },
    {
        question: "16. Which Indian hockey player is known as the \"Wizard of Hockey\"?",
        answer: "DHYAN CHAND"
    },
    {
        question: "17. Who was the captain of the Indian cricket team during the 1983 World Cup win?",
        answer: "KAPIL DEV"
    },
    {
        question: "18. Which Indian sports event is known as the \"World's Richest Race\"?",
        answer: "IPL"
    },
    {
        question: "19. Who became the first Indian to win an individual Olympic gold medal?",
        answer: "ABHINAV BINDRA"
    },
    {
        question: "20. Who became the first Indian chess player to achieve the title of Grandmaster?",
        answer: "VISHWANATH ANAND"
    }

    // Add more sports questions...
],
 "ENTERTAINMENT":[
    {
        question: "1. In the Hindi movie \"Zindagi Na Milegi Dobara,\" what were the three adventure sports",
        answer: "DEEP SEA DIVING,BULL RACE,SKY DIVING"
    },
    {
        question: "2. What was the original name of the series \"Money Heist\" in Spanish?",
        answer: "LA CASA DE PAPEL"
    },
    {
        question: "3. Who played the character of \"Iron Man\" in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
        answer: "ROBERT DOWNEY JR"
    },
    {
        question: "4. What is the name of the castle in the series \"Harry Potter\"?",
        answer: "HOGWARTS"
    },
    {
        question: "5. In the series \"Game of Thrones,\" what is the family motto of House Stark?",
        answer: "WINTER IS COMING"
    },
    {
        question: "6. What is Ross’s famous catchphrase in the TV series FRIENDS?",
        answer: "WE WERE ON A BREAK"
    },
    {
        question: "7. What is the name of Klaus Mikaelson’s brother who first appears in season 3?",
        answer: "ELIJAH MIKAELSON"
    },
    {
        question: "8. What is the full name of Elena’s adoptive father?",
        answer: "GRAYSON GILBERT"
    },
    {
        question: "9. What is the name of Joey's soap opera character?",
        answer: "DR.DAKE RAMORAY"
    },
    {
        question: "10. What is the name of the fictional African country in Black Panther?",
        answer: "WAKANDA"
    },
    {
        question: "11. Which movie is based on the life of Indian mathematician Shakuntala Devi?",
        answer: "SHAKUNTALA DEVI"
    },
    {
        question: "12. What is the name of the lead singer of the band Coldplay?",
        answer: "CHRIS MARTIN"
    },
    {
        question: "13. Which movie features the famous line, \"You can't handle the truth!\"?",
        answer: "A FEW GOOD MEN"
    },
    {
        question: '14. In the series "Friends," what is Joey\'s famous catchphrase?',
        answer: "HOW YOU DOIN"
    },
    {
        question: '15. What is the name of the fictional city in the "Batman" movies?',
        answer: "GOTHAM CITY"
    },
    {
        question: '16. In which Bollywood movie would you find the song "Chaiyya Chaiyya"?',
        answer: "DIL SE"
    },
    {
        question: '17. In the TV series "Breaking Bad," what is the profession of Walter White before he becomes a drug dealer?',
        answer: "CHEMISTRY TEACHER"
    },
    {
        question: "18. Which Indian movie won an Oscar for the song \"Jai Ho\"?",
        answer: "SLUMDOG MILLIONAIRE"
    },
    {
        question: "19. Which Bollywood movie features the famous dialogue, “Mogambo khush hua”?",
        answer: "MR.INDIA"
    },
    {
        question: '20. Which song from the movie "RRR" won the Golden Globe Award for Best Original Song in 2023?',
        answer: "NATU NATU"
    }

    
],
     "TECHNOLOGY":[
        {
            question: "1.What is part of a database that holds only one type of information?",
            options: ["A) report ", "B) feild", "C) Record", "D) file"],
            answer: "B"
        },
        {
            question: "2.'.MOV' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
            options: ["A) IMAGE FILE ", "B) ANIMATION FILE", "C) AUDIO FILE", "D) MS DOCS FILE"],
            answer: "B"
        },
        {
            question: ". Look at this series: 2, 1, (1/2), (1/4), ... What number should come next",
            options: ["A)1/3  ", "B) 1/8", "C)2/3 ", "D) 1/16"],
            answer: "B"
        },
        {
            question: "Which kind of planning consists of successive representations of different levels of a plan?",
            options: ["A) HIERARCHIAL PLANNING  ", "B) NON-HIERARCHIAL PLANNING", "C)PROJECT PLANNING ", "D)ALL OF THE ABOVE "],
            answer: "A"
        },
        {
            question: "4. Who invented mechanical calculator called Pascaline?",
            options: ["A. Charles Babbage", "B. Blaise Pascal", "C. Alan Turing","D. Lee De Forest"],
            answer: "A"
        },
        {
            question: "5. Who among the following considered as the 'father of artificial intelligence'?",
            options: ["A. Charles Babbage",  "B. Lee De Forest"," C. John McCarthy", "D.  JP Eckert"],
            answer: "B"
        },
        {
            question: "6. Which was the world's first successful electronic computer?",
            options: ["A. PARAM", "B. CRAY-1", "C. Pascaline", "D. ENIAC electronic Numerical Integrator and computer"],
            answer: "C"
        },
        {
            question: "7. Find out the correct definition of Wide Area Network (WAN)?",
            options: ["A. It is a programming language with strong abstraction from the details of the computer",
"B. It is a collection of computers interconnected with each other through cables to share their data, information and other common hardware resources",
"C. A computer network that covers a broad area (i.e., any network, whose communications links cross metropolitan, regional or national boundaries)",
"D. A  computer network covering a small physical area like a home, office or small groups of buildings, such as a school or an airport"],
            answer: "D"
        },
        {
            question: "8. Which of the following is also called translator?",
            options: ["A. Data representation",   "B. MS-DOS", "C. Operating System",   "D. Language Processor"],
            answer: "D"
        },
        {
            question: "9. How the quality of printer is measured?",
            options: ["A. Alphabet per strike ",  " B. Words per Inch","C. Strike per Inch",   "D. Dots per Inch"],
            answer: "D"
        },
        {
            question: "10. Name the scientist who first used a glass prism to obtain the spectrum of sunlight –",
            options: ["1) C.V. Raman",  " 2) Lord Rayleigh", "3) Isaac Newton", "4) S. Chandrasekhar"],
            answer: "3"
        },
        {
            question: "11. The world’s first ferry sailing on liquid hydrogen – MF Hydra, was commissioned by the –",
            options: ["1) German Company",  "2) Australian Company"," 3) Norwegian Company", " 4) Chinese Company"],
            answer: "3"
        },
        {
            question: "12. A geographical unit that collects, stores, and release water is called –",
            options: ["1) Watershed ",  "2) Waste land", "3) Wetland",    " 4) Water rese"],
            answer: "1"
        },
        {
            question: "13. NASA recently marks 10th anniversary of space shuttle disaster of",
            options: ["(A) Phoenix ",   "(B) Avenger", "(C) Discovery",  " (D) Columbia"],
            answer: "D"
        },
        {
            question: "14. Chandrayaan-2 Mission was launched by which vehicle?",
            options: ["A. GSLV MkIII ",  "B. PSLV C11","C. GSLV F11", " D. PSLV C45"],
            answer: "A"
        },
        {
            question: "15.Which is a type of Electrically-Erasable Programmable Read-Only Memory?",
            options: ["A. Flash", " B. Flange","C. Fury","D. FRAM"],
            answer: "A"
        },
        {
            question: "16 '.MPG' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
            options: ["A.	WordPerfect Document file ", "B. MS Office document","C.Animation/movie file ","D. Image file"],
            answer: "C"
        },
        {
            question: "17. In P-N junction, the region containing the uncompensated acceptor and donor ions is called",
            options: ["A.transition zone ",  "B. depletion region"," C.	neutral region ",  " D. active region"],
            answer: "B"
        },
        {
            question: "18. How long is an IPv6 address?",
            options: ["A. 32 bits", "B. 128 bytes", "C. 64 bits", "D. 128 bits"],
            answer: "D"
        },
        {
            question: "19. What command is used to create a backup configuration?",
            options: [" A. copy running backup","B. copy running-config startup-config","C. config mem "," D. wr mem"],
            answer: "B"
        },
        {
            question: "20. Odometer is to mileage as compass is to?",
            options: ["A.Speed", "B. hiking"," C. needle", " D. direction"],
            answer: "D"
        }

        
    ],
          "RIDDLES" : [
        {
            question: "1.I speak without a mouth and hear without ears. I have nobody, but I come alive with wind. What am I?",
            answer: "AN ECHO"

        },
        {
            question: "2. Two in a corner, one in a room, zero in a house, but one in a shelter. What am I?",
            answer: "LETTER R "

        },
        {
            question: "3.The more you take, the more you leave behind. What am I?",
            answer: "FOOTSTEPS"

        },
        {
            question: "4.. No matter how little or how much you use me, you change me every month. What am I?",
            answer: "CALENDAR"

        },
        {
            question: "5.If your uncle’s sister is not your aunt, what relation is she to you?",
            answer: "MOTHER"

        },
        {
            question: "6. Take one out and scratch my head, I am now black but once was red. What am I?",
            answer: "A MATCH"

        },
        {
            question: "7.Take one out and scratch my head, I am now black but once was red. What am I?",
            answer: "ENVELOPE"

        },
        {
            question: "8.What is so fragile that saying its name breaks it?",
            answer: "SILENCE"

        },
        {
            question: "9.A man goes out in heavy rain with nothing to protect him from it. His hair doesnt get wet. How does he do that?",
            answer: "BALD"

        },
        {
            question: "10.How many bananas can you eat if your stomach is empty?",
            answer: "1 BANANA"

        },
        {
            question: "11.What is harder to catch the faster you run?",
            answer: "BREATHE"

        },
        {
            question: "12.Which is heavier: a ton of bricks or a ton of feathers?",
            answer: " SAME "

        },
        {
            question: "13.You see me once in June, twice in November, and not at all in May. What am I? ",
            answer: "LETTER E "

        },
        {
            question: "14.I’m not alive, but I grow. I don’t have lungs, but I need air. I don’t have a mouth, but water kills me. What am I?",
            answer: "FIRE"

        },
        {
            question: "15.Poor people have it. Rich people need it. If you eat it you die. What is it?",
            answer: "NOTHING"

        },
        {
            question: "16.The more of this there is, the less you see. What is it?",
            answer: "DARKNESS"

        },
        {
            question: "17.What has a head and a tail but no body?",
            answer: "COIN"

        },
        {
            question: "18..  The cowboy rode into town on Friday. He stayed for five days and left on Friday. How?",
            answer: "HORSE NAME IS FRIDAY"

        },
        {
            question: "19. What can fill a room but takes up no space?",
            answer: "LIGHT"

        },
        {
            question: "20.I have branches, but no fruit, trunk or leaves. What am I?",
            answer: "BANK"

        }
    ]
};

export default questions;